eyeslipsface.co.uk 2016-12-02

# Makeup and Cosmetics | elf Cosmetics | EyesLipsFace.com | Privacy Policy

**e.l.f. Cosmetics Privacy Policy**

**This Privacy Policy was last updated on: 17 May 2016**

www.eyeslipsface.co.uk (the Website) is brought to you by e.l.f. Cosmetics, Inc. ("we"). This Privacy Policy describes the types of personal and other information we collect on the Website, how we use such information and to whom and under what circumstances we may disclose it. By accessing the Website on any computer, mobile phone, tablet, or other device (collectively, “Device”), you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and acknowledge that your information will be collected by e.l.f. Cosmetics, Inc.. a company established in the United States. If you do not agree to the policy, please do not use the Website.

We may modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on our Website. We encourage you to periodically review our Privacy Policy to stay informed about how we are using the information we collect.

**COLLECTION OF INFORMATION**

**Personal Information**

We collect personal information from you when you submit it to us, including by: (1) registering on the Website; (2) placing an order; (3) signing up for our newsletter; (4) contacting us; or (5) participating in a Website promotion or survey. This information may include, for example, your name, email address, mailing address, billing address, telephone number, date of birth, and credit or debit card information. We may combine the information we collect from you with information we receive about you from other sources, such as address update services.

We also allow users to provide us with their friend’s email addresses through the Website's refer-a-friend mechanism, so that we can send them information about our products and promotions.  You must ensure that before you provide us with personal information about another person (including e-mail addresses), you have their agreement to do so and that they are aware of the ways in which we use personal information as set out in this Privacy Policy.

We may collect personal information from you when you write a review on our site. However, we do not ask, and you should not enter, your full name anywhere in your review.

**Other Information**

When you visit the Website, we may collect certain other information from you, including your Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, operating system, the specific web pages visited during your connection, and the domain name from which you accessed the Website. In addition, we may collect information about your browsing behaviour, such as the date and time you visit the Website, the areas or pages of the Website that you visit, the amount of time you spend viewing the Website, the number of times you return to the Website and other clickstream data. We may also use non-personal information for statistical analysis, research, and other purposes.

_Cookies and Web beacons_

By using this Website you agree to our use of cookies. Like many commercial websites, we analyse how visitors use our Website through what is known as "cookie" technology. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer when you access the Website and allows us to recognize you each time you visit the Website. We may use cookies to: (1) allow you to use the Website without having to re-enter your user name and password; (2) enhance or personalize your Website usage and shopping experience; (3) monitor Website usage; (4) manage the Website; (5) improve the Website and our products and services; and (6) deliver adverts more relevant to you and your interests . If you choose, you can set your browser to reject cookies or you can manually delete individual or all of the cookies on your computer by following your browser’s help file directions. For more information about how to do this, and about cookies in general, you can visit: [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). However, if your browser is set to reject cookies or you manually delete cookies, you may have some trouble accessing and using some of the pages and features that are currently on our Website, or that we may put on our Website in the future.

We may also use web beacons on the Website, in our emails and in our advertisements on other websites. Web beacons are tiny graphic images that are used to collect information about your Website visit, such as the pages you view and the features you use, as well as information about whether you open and/or act upon one of our emails or advertisements. We may also collect the URL of the website you visited immediately before coming to the Website. Web beacons help us analyse our Website visitors' behaviour and measure the effectiveness of the Website and our advertising. We may work with service providers that help us track, collect and analyse this information.

We may combine the non-personal information we collect through cookies and web beacons with other information we have collected from you.

**Use of Information**

We may use the information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes: (1) to fulfil your requests for products; (2) to respond to your inquiries; (3) to review Website usage and operations; (4) to address problems with the Website, our business or our services; (5) to protect the security or integrity of the Website and our business; (6) to monitor the Website for compliance with our Terms of Use and the law; and (7) to contact you with Website updates, newsletters and other informational and promotional materials from us and third party marketing offers from our trusted partners, as well as from other companies.

If you do not wish to receive communications from us about special offers and promotions, you can opt-out of receiving these communications by following the instructions contained in the messages you receive. Even if you opt-out of receiving these messages, we reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the services we provide, and we may send you service announcements and administrative messages. We do not offer you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving those communications.

**Disclosure of Information**

We may disclose information collected from and about you as follows: (1) to our related companies and service providers, to perform a business, professional or technical support function for us; (2) to our marketing partners, advertisers or other third parties in an aggregated and anonymised form; (3) as necessary if we believe that there has been a violation of the Website Terms of Use or of our rights or the rights of any third party; (4) to respond to legal process (such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order) and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law; and (5) in the event that our company or substantially all of its assets are acquired, your personal information may be one of the transferred assets. We may also disclose your personal information with your express consent. We may share aggregate, non-personally identifiable information about Website users with third parties.

Please note that if you voluntarily submit any personal information for posting on the Website, such as a review or a blog post, the information becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others, so you should use care before posting information about yourself online.

**Access to Your Personal Information**

You may access your personal information by signing into your account. From there, you can correct or modify your information. Please ensure that you keep your personal and contact details up to date by signing into your account and making changes when required.

**Security**

We maintain reasonable and appropriate measures designed to maintain information we collect in a secure manner. We have taken certain physical, electronic, and administrative steps to safeguard and secure the information we collect from Website visitors.

Even though we follow reasonable procedures to try to protect the information in our possession, no security system is perfect and we cannot promise, and you should not expect, that your information will be secure in all circumstances. The transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure; this risk is common across the internet and not specific to our Website. We cannot guarantee the security of your data (including your personal information) transmitted to our Website; any transmission is at your own risk.

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computing device. Be sure to sign off and close your browser when you have finished your user session. This will help to ensure that others do not access your personal information if you share your computing device or use a computing device in a public place such as a library or internet café.

**Children**

We do not direct the Website to, nor do we knowingly collect any personal information from, children under the age of thirteen. In accordance with our terms and conditions of sale you must be at least eighteen years of age to order products from the Website.

**Third Party Websites**

The Website may contain links to third-party websites, such as social media sites like Facebook and Twitter, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the activities and practices that take place on these sites. Accordingly, we recommend that you review the privacy policy posted on any external site before disclosing any personal information. Please contact those websites directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

**Interest Based Advertising**

We may use third-party advertising companies that use tracking technologies to serve our advertisements across the Internet. These companies may collect anonymous information about your visits to the Website and other websites and your interaction with our advertising and other communications. These advertising companies serve ads on behalf of us and others on non-affiliated sites, and some of those ads may be personalized, meaning that they are intended to be relevant to you based on information collected about your visits to this site and elsewhere over time. Other companies may also use such technology to advertise on our Website.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We may change this privacy policy from time to time. When we do, we will post the change(s) on our Website. If we change the policy in a material way, we will provide appropriate online notice to you. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy.

**Contact Us**

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us by emailing us using the form at www.eyeslipsface.co.uk/contactus. If we need, or are required, to contact you concerning any event that involves your information, we may do so by email, telephone, or mail.
